jora.com 2014-12-24

# Jora.com

##  Privacy Statement 

Where used in this Statement, the term "personal information" has the meaning attributed to that term in the Privacy Act (Cth) 1988 (" **Privacy Act** "). 

This Statement has been prepared by Job Seeker Pty Ltd interchangeably referred to in this Statement as ("Jobseeker", "we", "us" and "our"). 

Users who log on to [www.jobsearch.net](http://www.jobsearch.net/) (“ **Site** ”) but do not create an account are referred to generically in this Statement as "users" or "you". 

Other definitions in this Statement include: 

" **Advertiser" or “Employer”** means users seeking employees for open employment position. 

**“Client”** means any job board, partner or company advertising through the Jobseeker Site. 

**“Company Logo”** means the Jobseeker Product offering in which the brand will appear in search results pages on all of the Employer or Advertiser Job Ads. 

“ **Job Ad** ” means an advertisement for an open employment position. 

“ **Proposal** ” means the quotation provided to the Client. 

“ **Plan** ” means credits purchased over a defined period for use on the Site. 

###  **Collecting information on Jobseeker visitors**

Jobseeker collects non-personal information on Site visits including, without limitation, which sections of the Site are most frequently visited, how often, and for how long. This data is always used as aggregated, non-personal information, and may be shared with Jobseeker partners to provide them with information relating to how Jobseeker visitors 'use' the Site. 

###  **IP Addresses**

Jobseeker's web servers gather your IP address to assist with the diagnosis of problems or support issues with our services, and to monitor the use of our Site. 

###  **Cookies & Applets**

Jobseeker uses cookies and applets to provide you with a better browsing experience and tailor advertisements that appear (on the Site or other websites) to your browsing preferences. 

Users who do not wish to have cookies active whilst they browse the Site can "opt out" by modifying the privacy options in your browser. However, doing so will prevent access to some areas of the Site and limit your use of some of the Jobseeker services. 

###  **Third Party Measurement**

In order to better understand our users, Jobseeker utilises a third party measurement tool called Google Analytics, to analyse Site traffic. A tracking code is used to collect the following information on the usage of the Site: 

· The number of page views (or page impressions) 

· The number of unique visitors 

· How long these unique visitors (on average) 

· Common entry and exit points into the Site 

This aggregate, non-personal information is collated and used by Jobseeker to assist in analysing the usage of the Site. 

###  **Collecting information on Jobseeker Registered Users**

As part of registering with Jobseeker, we collect personal information about Registered Users in order for Registered Users to take full advantage of Jobseeker services. 

  1. **Create an Account**

Creating an Account or registering on the Site is completely optional, and you do not need to register on the Site in order to submit a job application. However, registration allows you to take advantage of more of the tools, services and resources that may assist you in finding a job. To become a Registered User you will need to submit some personal information including your email address. You may access your information at any time by editing your profile under ‘My Account’.

Jobseeker may also use this information in order to customise the service we provide to you. 

  2. **Email Alerts**

Email Alerts are an optional service available to Users. Users can select to receive email alerts based on certain searches. Jobseeker will notify Users via email of jobs specific to their specified criteria. Users can modify or delete their Email Alert preferences (or their account) at any time by going to the 'My Activity' area of the Site.

  3. **Storing your resume**

Registered Users may upload and store a resume in Jobseeker, and use that resume when applying for a job. Deleting a resume will mean it is no longer accessible to the Registered User. Deleted records may still be stored by Jobseeker in testing or backup systems for a period of time. 

Your Resume can be set as Private of Public 

  * Public Resumes are resume is visible to Employers, and Employers can find and contact you via Jobseeker. 
  * Private Resumes are invisible to Employers and Employers cannot reach you. 

All information provided when uploading a resume (including your name, resume, email address, telephone numbers, employment and educational history) may be used by Jobseeker for the purpose of improving placement opportunities for you or for tailoring specific products to you. 

Registered Users can modify their resume at any time, or modify the privacy options in relation to their Resume settings at any time. 

You may also delete your Resume altogether. Deleted resumes may still however be stored by Jobseeker in testing or backup systems for a period of time. Jobseeker reserves the right to disable or clear a Resume at its sole discretion.

###  **Online Applications**

Making an online application to a job advertisement on Jobseeker is a free and optional service that does not require registration as a Registered User. 

Applications, including attachments and cover letters, are attained through the client’s own website via a link when selecting to apply for a job. 

###  **Storage & Security of Personal Information**

Jobseeker takes all reasonable steps to ensure the security of our system. Jobseeker allows you to access your information at any time to keep it accurate and up to date. Any information which we hold for you is stored on secure servers that are protected in controlled facilities. 

In addition, our employees and the contractors who provide services related to our information systems are obliged to respect the confidentiality and privacy of any personal information held by Jobseeker. However, Jobseeker will not be held responsible for events arising from unauthorised access of your personal information. 

You can also play an important role in keeping your personal information secure, by maintaining the confidentiality of any password and accounts used on the Site. Please notify us immediately if there is any unauthorised use of your account by any other Internet user, or any other breach of security relating to your account. 

###  **Data Transfers**

Sometimes, we transfer or disclose information to 3rd party contractors including to persons and businesses outside Australia. By giving us your personal information, you consent to such disclosures. Where we transfer information to persons outside Australia we believe that the recipients of such information are subject to a law, binding scheme or contract which effectively upholds principles for fair handling of the information that are similar in all material respects to the Australian Privacy Principles outlined in the Privacy Act. 

###  **Links**

Jobseeker may create links to other web sites. By clicking on these links on Jobseeker you may be transferred to an external website. Jobseeker is not responsible for the privacy of these other websites, and it is your responsibility to review those websites privacy statements, 

###  **Privacy & Site Changes**

From time to time, Jobseeker may review and update its Privacy Statement. Revised versions will be updated on the Site.
